Guide to the Stanford University, Michelle R. Clayman Institute for Gender Research, Records SC0705
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Records, Accession ARCH-2008-317
  - Proposal: WEEA: "Educational Leadership", 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Proposal Appendices, 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - INDIVIDUAL: Letters/brochures sent (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - INDIVIDUALS: Carolyn Charles (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Individual: Caroline Charles Lecture (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Individual: Constine, Nancy (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Individual: Conway, Bob (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Individuals: Beth Garfield (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - GSO/ S. DONALDSON: DONATION (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - KATHERINE GRAHAM (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - GUMAS, NATALIE--Library Donation (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Individual: Mr. and Mrs. Wallace (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - CORO: Joyce Ream, Richard Buttrick (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Insitiutes--Center for Policy Research (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - INSTITUE / CORPORATION: INVESTOR RESPONSIBILITY RESCH. CENTER (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Insitiute for the Future (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Institute--Libby Cater Aspen Institute (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Kennedy Institute--Women in Research (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Soroptimists (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Government: RFP for Displaced Homemakers Center Evlauation, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - RANN, Fund for Improvement of Post-secondary Education, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - WEEA--Request for Porposal (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - GOVERNMENT GRANTS: Women's Education Equity Program H.E.W. (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Women without Boarders 2004 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Cornelia Gothe Center for Woemn's and Gender Studies (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - HEW Contacts (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Office of Education: Women's Action Program (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Advisory Committee: Women's Educational Equity Act (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - WISE--Student letter template (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - WISE--Facilitatiors (stud) (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - WISE--Students 2002 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - WISE--Faculty, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - WISE Invoices, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - WISE Correspondence, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - WISE June 2001 Correspond. (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - WISE Faculty Letter template (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - WISE Faculty, Fall 2001 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - WISE--Faculty, Summer 2001 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - WISE -- Students, Fall 2001 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - WISE--Students, Summer 2001 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - WISE Invoices, 2001--2002 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Newsletter 2003 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Newsletter 2002 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Newsletter 2001 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Newsletter 2000 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Brochure 2004 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Newsletter Info '04: Newsletter--Fall 2004 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Newsletter Info '04: Newsletter--Winter 2004 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - International Networks: Science and Society, IKNOW, Oct 2004 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - The Wall Street Journal: Two-Career Couples, July 29, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Draft: WEEA Proposal, 1 of 2 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Draft: WEEA Proposal, 2 of 2 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Persons, Professions and Sex: The Challenge of Changing Roles (CROW) (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - "Grads vs Undergrads" (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Peer Counseling Course Outline, March 1975 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - 1975-76 Management Seminar Series of the Business and Professional Women's Foundation (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Career Awareness Project (CAP) (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Business Week, Sept 15th, 1975 Where education is losing touch / Questions for… (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Project to Expand Women's Job Options, Center for Res of Women, Wellesley College (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Ann Seidman, Project on Expanding Women's Career Options, to Cynthia Davis (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Notes (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Notes on Career Planning Program, Sept 23, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - "Women In The Job Interview," Survey of Emoloyers 1973-74 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Application submission to Comprehensive Program, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Annotated Bibliography, Career Counsling: New Perspectives for Women and Girls (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Scholars A-C: Ancheta, Rebecca, 1 of 3 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Scholars A-C: de Bellaigue, Christina, 2 of 3 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Scholars A-C: Chu, Judy AS, 3 of 3 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Scholars D-N: Gardner, Kara AS, 1 of 3 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Scholars D-N: Kerr, Laura AS, 2 of 3 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Scholars D-N: Mahowald, Mary AS, 1 of 3 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Scholars O: O'Farrell, Brigid (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Scholars P-S: Pridmore-Brown, Michelle, 1 of 3 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Scholars P-S: Sellery, J'Nan Morse, 2 of 3 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Scholars P-S: Silverberg, Alice, 3 of 3 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Scholars T-Z: Turan, Janet Milzan, 1 of 5 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Scholars T-Z: Wardley, Lynn 2 of 5 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Scholars T-Z: Wayne, Tiffany AS, 3 of 5 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Scholars T-Z: Turan, Wojcicki, Janet AS, 4 of 5 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Scholars T-Z: Zahedi, Ashraf, 5 of 5 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Affiliated Scholars 2002-3: Inquiries 2002--2003, 1 of 2 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Affiliated Scholars 2002-3: Applicants: Affliated Scholar Renewals, 2 of 2 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Scholars '02, '03 and '04: 2003--2004 Scholars, ID Cards, correspondence, meetings, 1 of 4 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Scholars '02, '03 and '04: Scholars Program 2003, 2 of 4 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Scholars '02, '03 and '04: Scholars 2003-2004 Orientation Packets, 3 of 4 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Scholars '02, '03 and '04: 2002-2003 Scholars, 4 of 4 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Scholars--Past: 2001-2002 Scholars, 1 of 20 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Scholars--Past: 2000-2001 Scholars, 2 of 20 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Scholars--Past: 1999-2000 Scholars, 3 of 20 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Scholars--Past: 2001-2002 Scholars, 4 of 20 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Scholars--Past: 1998-1999 Scholars, 5 of 20 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Scholars--Past: 1997-1998 Scholars, 6 of 20 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Scholars--Past: 1996-1997 Scholars, 7 of 20 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Scholars--Past: 1995-1996 Scholars, 8 of 20 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Scholars--Past: 1994-1995 Scholars, 9 of 20 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Scholars--Past: 1993-1994 Scholars, 10 of 20 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Scholars--Past: 1992-1993 Scholars, 11 of 20 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Scholars--Past: 1991-1992 Scholars, 12 of 20 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Scholars--Past: 1990-1991 Scholars, 13 of 20 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Scholars--Past: 1989-1990 Scholars, 14 of 20 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Scholars--Past: 1988-1989 Scholars, 15 of 20 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Scholars--Past: 1987-1988 Scholars, 16 of 20 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Scholars--Past: 1986-1987 Scholars, 17 of 20 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Scholars--Past: 1985-1986 Scholars, 18 of 20 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Scholars--Past: 1984-1985 Scholars, 19 of 20 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Scholars--Past: Scholar Email Accounts 1996-2000, 20 of 20 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Scholars 01-02 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Bios, Addresses, ER 2001 -2002 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Corporate Breakfast Seminars 2001: Speaker 2001- Laura Canty Swapp, 1 of 6 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Corporate Breakfast Seminars 2001: Possible Speakers, 2 of 6 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Corporate Breakfast Seminars 2001: 2000-2001, Corporate Solicitation/Contact, 3 of 6 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Corporate Breakfast Seminars 2001: Corporate Bfast Seminars 2001, 4 of 6 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Corporate Breakfast Seminars 2001: Corporate Contact/Resources, 5 of 6 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Corporate Breakfast Seminars 2001: Collaboration for March 20th/01, 6 of 6 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Program Evaluations 2001: Bfast Seminar Series, 1 of 7 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Program Evaluations 2001: Associates Program, 2 of 7 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Program Evaluations 2001: Scholars' Program, 3 of 7 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Program Evaluations 2001: Senior Scholars Program, 4 of 7 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Program Evaluations 2001: Jing Lyman Lecture Series, 5 of 7 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Program Evaluations 2001: Graduate Dissertation Fellowship, 6 of 7 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Program Evaluations 2001: Difficult Dialogues Program, 7 of 7 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - 2004-2005 Scholars: 2004-2005 Scholars, 1 of 4 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - 2004-2005 Scholars: Scholars at other Institutions, 2 of 4 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - 2004-2005 Scholars: Visiting Scholar 2004, Azumi Tsuge, 3 of 4 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - 2004-2005 Scholars: Visiting Scholar Christina de Bellaigue, '04-'05, 4 of 4 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - 1994-05 Graduate Dissertation Fellowship Call for Applications (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Changing Families 2007, Difficult Dialogues II, Abandoned Final Report (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - "Scholars" (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Taglines 2006 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Women in Business 1 databese Project 2006 (Aborted) (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Women In Business Website (wibw) 2005-06 (Aborted) 1 of 2 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Women In Business Website (wibw) 2005-06 (Aborted) 2 of 2 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Stanford Executive Institute: Women and Leadership (1994) (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Balancing Work and Family Tape 1 of 4, 10-16-04; 1 audiocassette(s) (dat) (Box 21)
  - Family Diversity Tape 2 of 4, 10-16-04; 1 audiocassette(s) (dat) (Box 21)
  - Families, What Children Tape 3 of 4, 10-16-04; 1 audiocassette(s) (dat) (Box 21)
  - Promoting Marriage Tape 4 of 4, 10-16-04; 1 audiocassette(s) (dat) (Box 21)
  - Donor Relations, McCaw 6:15pm--7:30pm, 11/3/04; videotape (Mini DV) (Box 21)
  - DD2 Files, March 7, 2003; 2 computer file(s) (doc) (Box 21)
  - Family Diversity 10-16-04 Disc 2 of 2, 1 optical disc (CD-ROM) (Box 21)
  - Promoting Marriage 10-16-04 Disc 1 of 2, 1 optical disc (CD-ROM) (Box 21)
  - Promoting Marriage 10-16-04 Disc 2 of 2, 1 optical disc (CD-ROM) (Box 21)
  - Balancing Work and Family 10-16-04 Disc 1 of 2, 1 optical disc (CD-ROM) (Box 21)
  - Balancing Work and Family 10-16-04 Disc 2 of 2, 1 optical disc (CD-ROM) (Box 21)
  - What Children and Families Need to Thrive 10-16-04 Disc 1 of 3, 1 optical disc (CD-ROM) (Box 21)
  - What Children and Families Need to Thrive 10-16-04 Disc 2 of 3, 1 optical disc (CD-ROM) (Box 21)
  - Winter Seminar--Marilyn Yalom, 2/27/92; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - Health Seminar--Herant Katchadeurian--"Female Sexuality", 2/27/92; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - IRWG Open House Remarks, 5/14/97; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - 98 RR5 3B, about 5 min only, end of, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - Rick Banks, 1/29/03; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - Richard Banks--Jing Lyman Lecture Series, 1/29/03; 1 videotape(s) (dvcam) (Box 21)
  - Advertising--Feminist Radio Network, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - Breslin, Glenna / Falks, Candice, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - Barrett, Michelle--Apr 9 Crow Group, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - Feb 27th News, Feb 14th News, Feb 16th Hoops, Aug 9th Sports, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - Giuidice, Linda, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - History of Am. Women's Movem.(#25) / Women and the healthcare sys (#70), 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - Kusche, Brigitte, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - The Men's Program (#86), 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - Palmer, Judy--Glharch 1991, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - Rothwell, Shelia, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - Safer, Marilyn--May 25th, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - "Sexism" (#20) / Sexist Practice in America (#9), 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - Spiritsong, Mary Watkins, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - SRIT--Part I: Book 2, Case 1--Book 2 case 17 / Book 2 case 18--Book 2 case 29, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - SRIT--Part I: Book 2, Case 1--Book 2 case 17 / Book 2 case 18--Book 2 case 29, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - Women and Stress, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - Unlabeled tape #1, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - Unlabeled tape #2, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - Unlabeled tape #3, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - Unlabeled tape #4, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - DDI: Aging in the 21st Century, 11/09/00; 5 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - DDI: Aging in the 21st Century, 11/10/00; 5 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - DDI: Aging in the 21st Century, 01/12/01; 3 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - DDI: Aging in the 21st Century, 01/13/01; 5 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - DDI: Aging in the 21st Century, 01/15/01; 5 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - DDI: A Forum on Gender and Society, 03/30/01; 4 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - DDI: A Forum on Gender and Society, 03/31/01; 5 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - DDI: Aging in the 21st Century, 05/04/01; 3 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - DDI: Aging in the 21st Century, 05/05/01; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - DDI: A Forum on Gender and Society, 05/25/01; 4 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - DDI: A Forum on Gender and Society, 05/26/01; 5 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - Ms. Foundation Conference, 10/17/04; 5 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - 5/2 Difficult Dialogues, 3 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - 5/3 Difficult Dialogues, 4 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - DD2 Planning committee meeting, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - Campus Faculty Club dinner, 3/30/2000; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - Fall 1992 Jung Layman Lectures: Andrew Lisac, 11/18/92; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - WINSE, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - unlabeled, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
  - Difficult Dialogues: Aging in the 21st Century (1-12-01), 1 computer file(s) (doc)
  - Difficult Dialogues: Aging in the 21st Century (1-13-01), 1 computer file(s) (doc)
  - Transcripts, May 2-3-2002; 2 computer file(s) (doc) (Box 21)
  - Difficult Dialogues 2: 11/11 &11/12 Sessions, 3 computer file(s) (doc)
  - Consensus Report, computer files (Box 21)
  - DD1 Images, computer files (Box 21)
  - Grassroots experience, DTC prez, Storeishakti, 2 computer file(s) (ppt)
  - Difficult Dialogues Photos, 131 computer file(s)
  - IRWG, 2001; 39 computer file(s) (jpg) (Box 21)
  - Difficult Dialogues Mtg, 2001 Jan 12-13; 69 computer file(s)
  - Difficult Dialogues: Aging in the 21st Century: Town Hall Meeting, 2001-05-4; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 21)
  - Female Black Panther Party, May 1998; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 21)
  - Get Real: Straight Talk About Women's Health, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 21)
  - Hallo Hanine, Kora Terry, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 21)
  - unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 21)
  - DD2 Photos (Box 21)
  - Photo (Black and White), 1891-1991 T-shirt (Box 22)
  - Sex Bias slides (Box 22)
  - Stanford Institute for Research / Women and Gender (Box 22)
  - Difficult Dialogue Photos from Jan Meeting, 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 22)
  - Associate's Board Photos: 2000-2001? Includes Laura Carstensen (Box 22)
  - Photos, 11/13/2000; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 22)
  - Photos, 11/13/2000; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 22)
  - "Declaration of American Women, 1977" (80 Slides) (Box 22)
  - Women in United States History (Box 22)
  - Free Tear sheet with notes (Box 22)
- Records, Accession ARCH-2015-091
  - Uncovering Authentic Leadership (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Center for the Advancement of Women's Leadership (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Center for the Advancement of Women's Leadership--40 years of gender research, 2014-05-21 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Femtastic, 2014 Jan (Box 1, Folder 4)